# **Andrew Kurano**

Website Portfolio: <a href="https://andku23.github.io/">https://andku23.github.io/</a> 808-398-7638 • akurano@hawaii.edu

# **Objective**

Seeking job in tech field where I can learn to use my experience in 3D modeling, shaders, and high level programming to bridge the gap between art and coding

# **Skills**

Wide experience in creating 3D models in Blender from simple modeling to rigging and animating. Intermediate knowledge in using other programs such as ZBrush and Maya. Can create PBR textures and hand-painted texture maps in Substance Painter. Proficient knowledge in both high level coding such as C#, Java, and Python, as well as lower level languages such as C and CG. Extensive experience in integrating art and code in the Unity Game Engine and developing for mobile, PC and AR/VR.

# **Education**

**University of Hawaii at Manoa**, College of Engineering Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

**Spring 2018** 

# **Competitions**

## AT&T Hackathon 2018

# **Awarded First Place in Game Design**

- Created AR tower defense game where player uses physical environment as in-game environment
- Modeled all 3D props and programmed network system where client could log in from separate computer and control turrets in co-op mode

## **Global Game Jam 2018**

## **Awarded First Place in Diversity**

- Created game where player control robots to clean a floor, however robots react differently to each input and all robots must be controlled at the same time
- Modeled all 3D props, character, and vehicles

## **Global Game Jam 2017**

#### **Awarded Best Overall**

• Modeled selection of 3D props and characters, set up variable character proportions using blendshapes

## **Unity Projects**

# **HoloSage: Augmented Reality Training Tool**

Fall 2017 - Present

- Augmented Reality Tool allowing user to take holographic notes in the 3D environment as well as playback notes in real time
- Designed entire project structure from scratch in Unity using HoloToolkit API
- Lead further creation and instructed new programmers who joined project

## Alexa the Game

# **Summer 2017 - Present**

- Small scale sword combat game to experience entire game development workflow from concept art to finished product
- Modeled, rigged, textured, and animated all models and environments
- Programmed features such as interactable objects through abstract interfaces
- Worked alongside programmer to create finished game

# **Andrew Kurano**

Website Portfolio: <a href="https://andku23.github.io/">https://andku23.github.io/</a> 808-398-7638 • akurano@hawaii.edu

**Engineering Projects** 

Wifi Alarm Clock Fall 2016

• Alarm clock phone app that allows user to set alarms that only go off when connected to certain wifis thus avoiding unwanted alarms during class and meetings

• Wrote project in modified Java using Android Studios

Server/ Client Demo Spring 2017

• Server/Client project in C that could ping, download, and determine hierarchy in node tree

**Work Experience** 

# **Laboratory of Advanced Visualization and Applications**

**Summer 2017- Present** 

- Worked as both an artist and programmer to create VR/AR demos and video games
- Learned development process for VR, AR, and Mixed Reality
- Created HoloSage AR training tool for Navy requested project

# **Native Hawaiian Society of Engineers**

Spring 2016 - Present

- Worked as web designer to provide online community for aspiring Native Hawaiian Engineers
- Taught self HTML, CSS, databases and javascript to design webpage
- Handled communication between upper-level faculty and students

# **References**

• References and supporting documents will be furnished upon request